[Music]
[音乐]
let's use this extra method to say hi
让我们用这个额外的方法打招呼
welcome to spring i/o from my site
欢迎从我的网站春季到I / O
interesting that so many people show up
有趣的是，有很多人出现
I was assuming that everyone in this
我当时以为每个人
building microservices these days is
这几天建立微服务是
that what what you're talking oh that's
那你在说什么哦
not what I'm going to talk about today
不是我今天要谈论的
what I want to talk about is basically
我想说的基本上是
what you can do to keep structure alive
您可以做些什么来保持结构的活力
in your let's say more monolithic
在你说更单片
application I want to start with
我想开始的应用程序
contextualizing okay what I think this
情境化好了我怎么想
is is something worth while pursuing and
追求是值得的，
we're going to get into a bit of the up
我们将要进入​​一点点
benefits and downsides of Microsoft's
微软的优势和劣势
applications but then it's going to
应用程序，但随后
become pretty technical I have a tiny
变得非常技术我有一个小小的
boot extension I want to I want to show
我要显示的启动扩展名
you that will help you actually
你会帮助你实际上
maintaining that structure and achieving
保持结构并实现
it quite a few other goals that people
人们还有很多其他目标
usually have when they go to micro
当他们去微型时通常
services so that might be something that
服务，所以可能是
you're not even or you don't even have
你甚至没有，甚至没有
to move to micro services for to
转向微服务
actually achieve those goals but first
真正实现这些目标，但首先
things first my name is only what mom
事情首先我的名字只有妈妈
I've been mostly known for working on
我一直以工作着称
spend data project they've been summary
花费数据项目，他们一直在总结
organizations and team structure
组织和团队结构
recently but I'm still part of the team
最近，但我仍然是团队的一员
still doing that but focusing a bit more
仍然这样做，但要集中一点
on all the other stuff that has always
在所有其他的东西上
surrounded my work in Spring data just
在Spring数据中包围了我的工作
as the modulus stuff architectural
作为模数的东西建筑
framework stuff what-have-you I quickly
框架的东西我很快就拥有了
want to summarize some of the trades
想总结一些交易
that you get with these two different or
你得到这两个不同的或
opposing architectural styles I'm not
反对我不是的建筑风格
trying to cover everything or have a
试图掩盖一切或有一个
detailed comparison I much rather want
我比较想要详细的比较
to focus on of certain aspects that I
专注于某些方面
think make this alternative approach
认为采用这种替代方法
quite appealing and interesting so the
非常吸引人和有趣，所以
fundamental idea is that we have four
基本思想是我们有四个
concepts that we
我们的概念
have to sort of consider one is a bonded
必须考虑一个是保税区
context which is kind of some logical
某种逻辑上的上下文
structure within your within your
你内在的结构
application some your logical units the
应用一些逻辑单元
order management the customer management
订单管理客户管理
shipment supplies what-have-you we have
货运供应我们所拥有的
deployment units the question of what
部署单位的问题
kind of deployments
种类的部署
actually make up our overall system we
实际上构成了我们的整体系统
have internal invocations within those
在这些内部有内部调用
deployment units and we have external
部署单位，我们有外部
invocations across deployment units
跨部署单元的调用
right because it's it's different
对，因为这是不同的
processes so with microphone or list
麦克风或列表处理
it's basically a bounded context within
这基本上是一个有限的上下文
a single deployment unit and we all are
一个部署单元，我们都是
invoke Ross module invocations are
调用Ross模块的调用是
internal ones with whereas with micro
内部与微
services we sort of tie the the
我们将服务与
deployment unit to the bounded context
部署单元到有限的上下文
that's the fundamental idea right which
这是基本的想法
also means that we now these
也意味着我们现在这些
interactions now all of a sudden get
互动现在突然变得
cross project invocations right with all
所有人都可以跨项目调用
their ups and down sides so while it's
他们的起伏不定
probably less likely that you by
可能不太可能
accident just invoke some components via
事故只是通过调用一些组件
HTTP and the microservices world it's
HTTP和微服务世界
pretty easy to do so in a monolithic
整体上很容易做到
arrangement where you have a just a
你只有一个安排
spring beam and you just put an ad or
弹簧梁，而您只投放广告或
two wired to some other class and some
两个连接到其他班级和一些
other module and then you're just like
其他模块，然后您就像
wire this thing up and can call a method
连接这个东西，可以调用一个方法
on it
在上面
all right that's that's how how these
好吧，这就是这些
these architectures especially on the
这些架构，特别是在
left side degrade very quickly and we
左侧很快退化，我们
really want to have a look at how we
真的想看看我们
what we can actually do to keep this
我们实际上可以做些什么来保持这一点
this structure in the on there on the
这个结构在
left side around so the benefits I see
左侧左右，所以我看到的好处
on on an on a more monolithic approach
在一个更整体的方法上
is that we caught the idea again
是我们再次抓住了这个主意
fundamentally deploying multiple bounded
从根本上部署多个边界
context in the single deployment unit a
单个部署单元中的上下文
benefit especially when you start a new
受益，特别是当您开始新的
project when you're when you explore new
当您探索新项目时
ground it's that the the bounded context
理由是有限的上下文
boundaries are much easier to refactor
边界更容易重构
then if you started with with a
然后，如果您以
microservices project where you just
您所处的微服务项目
basically put api's in place and by the
基本上将api放在适当的位置
very first time you deploy these things
第一次部署这些东西
you have to now all of a sudden arrange
你现在必须突然安排
like breaking changes
喜欢打破变化
changes in general or what-have-you so
总体变化或您有什么变化
moving code around is much easier in a
在一个环境中移动代码要容易得多
in a same monolithic codebase right it's
在同一个整体的代码库中，它是
very easy to test the system overall we
总体上非常容易测试系统
can just like use spring integration
就像使用spring集成一样
test functionality we just bootstrap the
测试功能，我们只是引导
thing just call methods invoke REST API
事情只是调用方法调用REST API
is what have you right so it's it's
你是对的，就是
pretty easy as I said the chance for
正如我所说的那样，这很容易
degradation is given and it's that it's
给出了退化，这是
actually in place is one of the reasons
实际到位是原因之一
that so many people look into
这么多人关注
micro-services so just like that
像这样的微服务
well-defined structure that we all
我们大家定义良好的结构
started with then over over the course
在整个过程中开始
of time basically degrading and that
时间基本上会退化，
making the further development of the
使之进一步发展
system much more complicated and what's
系统要复杂得多，这是什么
also not really easy or like I haven't
也不是很容易，或者像我还没有
seen anyone really approaching this
看到有人真正接近这个
before is how do you actually test
之前是如何实际测试的
individual modules we can get into the
我们可以进入的各个模块
question of like structuring your your
像构造你的你的问题
monolithic application you can of course
您当然可以使用单片应用程序
use like things like maven modules or
使用类似Maven模块之类的东西
greater modules or what-have-you to
更大的模块或您拥有什么
structure your your monolith internally
内部构造您的整体
but just like bootstrapping let's say
但是就像引导一样
two or three of them together in
其中两个或三个一起
combination without too much effort
无需太多努力的组合
isn't like really a first-class citizen
真的不是一流的公民
in the in the testing support in Spring
在Spring的测试支持中
Framework or spam booty framework or
框架或垃圾邮件赃物框架或
hasn't been so far actually for
实际上到目前为止还没有
microservices the downsides I see and
我看到微服务的缺点
met actually coming to the goals that I
真正实现了我的目标
want to achieve with stuff I sort of
想用我喜欢的东西实现
have prepared here is that the bound
这里准备的是
context interaction is remote that means
上下文交互是远程的，这意味着
instead of a local method call that can
而不是可以
either succeed or throw an exception we
无论成功还是抛出异常，我们
can now have we now have to serialize
现在可以拥有我们现在必须序列化
the payload we have to invoke a network
我们需要调用网络的有效负载
call which is much more expensive much
通话费用高得多
more failure scenarios right the other
其他更多的故障场景
system could not be available the system
系统无法使用
could be available but the network could
可能可用，但网络可以
not be available what have you so
无法获得你有什么
there's a lot of stuff you have to do
有很多事情要做
that you actually have to guard against
您实际上要提防的
and then add extra code to sort of
然后添加一些额外的代码
mitigate those problems right hystrix
缓解这些问题
these kinds of things which ironically
这些具有讽刺意味的事情
sort of the first your your actual focus
首先是您的实际关注点
from writing business code to oh I need
从编写业务代码到我需要
to put this historic stuff here and what
把这个历史性的东西放在这里
have you so you basically focused on on
你有没有，所以你基本上专注于
integration on the infrastructure level
基础架构级别的集成
um testing individual individual modules
um测试单个模块
is fine works pretty well the reason I
很好很好的原因是我
marked this with yellow is that when you
用黄色标记的是当您
have a lot of interaction between the
之间有很多互动
components it's not only an indicator
不仅是一个指标
that you're kind of set up is or your
您的设置类型或您的
your granularity is maybe it's something
您的粒度也许是
you should you should work on the you
你应该在你身上工作
also run into the situation that you
也遇到你的情况
have to bootstrap other systems stop or
必须引导其他系统停止或
mock other systems to actually
模拟其他系统以实际
integration test those modules which can
集成测试那些可以
be quiet or can introduce quite a bit of
保持安静或可以引入很多
effort as well as I said refer
以及我所说的努力
refactoring context boundaries sorry
重构上下文边界抱歉
it's quite a significant effort because
这是相当大的努力，因为
once API so public especially if you
曾经的API如此公开，特别是如果您
have these individual services managed
管理这些个人服务
by different teams then it's not only
由不同的团队，这不仅是
technical decisions and it's political
技术决策和政治决策
decisions can the other team actually
决定可以由其他团队实际完成
change that API for you how do you
为您更改该API
manage other clients that have relied on
管理其他依赖的客户
the previous API yeah they are they are
以前的API是的，它们是
you you're talking like interaction on
你说的就像互动
on a completely different level right
在完全不同的水平上
rather than just like refactoring using
而不是像使用
your refactoring capabilities of your
您的重构能力
IDE to just like change a method name or
IDE就像更改方法名称或
a property name or what have you and
财产名称或您有什么
what's also quite a challenge is that
还有一个挑战是
how do you actually test the system
您如何实际测试系统
overall how do we actually test like a
总的来说，我们如何实际测试像
business flow from end to end we need to
我们需要从头到尾的业务流程
bootstrap all the systems we have to
引导我们必须拥有的所有系统
have them around and yeah then we can
有他们在附近，是的，我们可以
just we also need to trace the calls
只是我们还需要跟踪电话
that probably happen between the systems
这可能发生在系统之间
and that's that's quite a challenge so
那就是很大的挑战，所以
especially the like the testing
尤其喜欢测试
individual modules and aspect is
各个模块和方面是
something that people often start with
人们通常从开始
with Mike oh that's that's the reason
和迈克在一起那就是原因
they start with micro services in the
他们从微服务开始
first place because they want to achieve
因为他们想实现第一名
that right there's no way you can really
那是不可能的，你真的可以
nicely bootstrap a part of a spring
很好地引导弹簧的一部分
application
应用
I mean how would that work right so and
我的意思是这样会如何工作，
that's something that I basically took a
这是我基本上采取的
closer look at and turned out it turned
仔细看看，原来变成了
it actually into into this into this
它实际上变成了这个
particular project that I want to show
我想展示的特定项目
you and I have this applied through a
您和我已通过
sample code base that itself or intern
本身或实习生的示例代码库
is developed in a project that I'm
是在我所从事的项目中开发的
having with the local university in my
在我当地的大学里
hometown
家乡
they're basically letting students in
他们基本上是让学生进入
third semesters of software engineering
软件工程学期
build a web application with spring boot
使用Spring Boot构建Web应用程序
what could possibly go wrong right they
他们可能会出什么问题
don't have no I mean half a semester of
没有，我是说半个学期
Java expertise no database lectures
Java专业知识，无数据库讲座
before it's it's really fun to watch and
观看之前真的很有趣
interesting but we basically provide
有趣，但我们基本上提供
them with sort of a skeleton application
它们具有基本的应用程序
that's centered around an e-commerce
以电子商务为中心
application framework sort of it has a
应用程序框架有一个
set of business modules so we have we
业务模块集，所以我们有
have users abstracted we have orders
有用户抽象我们有订单
abstracted we have a catalog and an
摘要我们有一个目录和一个
inventory which basically catalogue has
目录基本具有的库存
products right general descriptions
产品权的一般描述
prices inventory has products plus a
价格清单包含产品加
certain amount so we basically stop
一定数量，所以我们基本上停止了
keeping and the orders refer to products
保持和订单指的是产品
and the catalog so they have a or line
和目录，所以他们有一个或行
items that you can basically put into
基本上可以放入的物品
the order and whenever you complete an
订单以及每当您完成
order
订购
there's API for the inventory to update
有用于库存更新的API
the stock right so if I'm ordering like
股票的权利，所以如果我要订购
five TVs the stock has to be reduced by
五台电视机的库存必须减少
five items for that particular product
该特定产品的五个项目
we also have the concept of business
我们也有商业的概念
time it actually what's going on like
时间实际上是怎么回事
from a business point of view in this
从商业角度来看
doesn't really matter for this for this
对此并不重要
for this presentation there's just a
对于此演示文稿，只有一个
couple of things that I want I wanted
我想要的几件事
you to focus on so I have the the solid
你要专注，所以我有扎实的
lines or the solid arrows are components
线或实心箭头是组件
dependencies which means in that module
依赖关系意味着在那个模块中
there is
有
a spring beam that has a reference to a
弹簧梁参考
spring beam in the inventory module
库存模块中的弹簧梁
right or the orders module has a spring
对或订单模块有弹簧
component that itself has a dependency
本身具有依赖性的组件
on business time I'm going to get to
在工作时间，我要去
that back in a second because that's
一秒钟回来，因为那是
it's really important that's really
真的很重要
something to to have a look at and to
值得一看的东西
keep an eye on when you're actually
当你真正在意
evolving those systems the other
不断发展这些系统
dependencies are plane type dependencies
依赖关系是平面类型的依赖关系
right so we have let's say the inventory
对的，所以我们说库存
has an inventory item which is
有一个库存项目是
effectively a product plus some amount
有效地加上一定数量的产品
right so let's JPA in this case it's JPA
好的，所以在这种情况下让我们的JPA是JPA
entities and that's just a plain type
实体，那只是一个普通的类型
dependency it's not like a swing
依赖它不像秋千
component you can see why that's
组件，您可以看到为什么
important I'm going to get back in a
重要的是我要回到
second and you already see like people
第二，你已经看到像人
that like maybe more senior or having it
也许更高级或更喜欢
like their app architect their glasses
就像他们的应用设计师一样
on they already see that there's a
他们已经看到有一个
problem in this in this in this code
此代码中的问题
base I am right okay so the the we're
基地，我没事，所以我们
going to see code in a bit I just want
我只想看一点代码
to start with the thing that I'm going
从我要去的东西开始
to show you it's called modulus like the
告诉你它叫做模数
term I know I didn't coin it I haven't
学期我知道我没有投币，我没有
really found an ultimate source for it I
真的找到了它的最终来源
originally used it in another talk I
最初是在我的另一个演讲中使用的
think a workshop I gave last year or two
认为我去年或两年间举办的研讨会
years ago here which is called
多年前这里被称为
refactoring to a system of systems where
重构到一个系统的系统
I basically suggested to but build a mod
我基本上建议但要建立一个mod
monolith in a certain way and to prepare
整体以某种方式准备
it for extraction into micro services
提取到微服务中
and this is there was a lot of feedback
这是很多反馈
that okay there's no real framework
好的，没有真正的框架
support for that kind of development no
对这种发展的支持
active day I mean there's not nothing
活跃的一天，我的意思是什么都没有
nothing is in the way between the
两者之间没有任何关系
framework and you to actually build
框架和您实际构建
something like this as well but out of
像这样的东西，但出于
the box there wasn't something usable so
盒子里没有可用的东西，所以
what's the idea so the idea is that we
是什么主意，所以主意是
sort of start with the question okay how
首先从问题开始，如何
do we map those logical modules bounded
我们是否映射那些有界的逻辑模块
contexts or how do you onto our code
上下文或您如何使用我们的代码
base because when the rubber hits the
因为橡胶碰到
road we mean this is this PowerPoint
路，我们的意思是这是PowerPoint
presentations are fine but at some point
演讲很好，但在某些时候
we have to find a means to represent the
我们必须找到一种方法来代表
customer or the orders module in the
客户或订单模块
countryside and the fundamental
农村与基本面
assumption is that with within your
假设是
spring application you usually have the
春季申请，您通常有
application class in the top level
顶层的应用程序类
package and then you have business
包，然后你有业务
packages right underneath that so that's
封装在其下方，因此
that's basically the thing here right so
这基本上就是这里的事情，所以
you could go ahead and put your
你可以继续把你的
application class in the very top level
最顶层的应用程序类
modulus package and then in my example
模数封装，然后在我的示例中
case he would have dot orders we would
如果他有点订单，我们会
have done inventory dot what-have-you
已经完成库存点你有什么
right so just package by by component is
对，所以只按组件包装是
if you to speak about it in Simon Browns
如果您在西蒙·布朗斯（Simon Browns）谈论它
terms he has a lot of has a decent
他有很多的条件
talked about that I've had it like five
谈到我有五个
or six years ago I could travelling
或六年前，我可以旅行
conferences were the talk that was
会议是当时的话题
called oops where did my architecture go
叫哎呀，我的建筑去了哪里
if you if you googled for dads there's a
如果您用谷歌搜索爸爸，
blog post about that why I think that
关于为什么我认为的博客文章
kind of top-level structure at least is
至少是一种顶层结构
a decent start has a lot of consequences
良好的开端有很多后果
about disability rules because we can
关于残疾规则，因为我们可以
use the java package scope here to hide
在这里使用java包范围隐藏
components from the outside it's kind of
从外部来的组件
interesting I'm going to come back to
有趣的是，我要回到
that in a second but that's the
一秒钟，但这就是
fundamental idea right and then we can
基本概念正确，然后我们可以
make use of that by but by just one tiny
利用这一点，但只有一点点
change which is exchanging that aspirin
交换阿司匹林的变化
boot application with add modulus and
启动应用程序，添加模数和
that's basically designed to the to the
基本上是针对
to the library that that you opt into
到您选择的图书馆
this package structure there are a lot
这个包的结构有很多
of knobs and additional annotations
旋钮和其他注释
where you can also use different kinds
在这里你也可以使用不同的种类
of packet structures to make it work
数据包结构以使其正常工作
with that kind of system but by default
使用这种系统，但默认情况下
you don't need to do anything but change
除了改变，你什么都不需要做
that annotation and actually at system
该注释，实际上是在系统上
runtime that that of course in turn is
当然，运行时
annotated with at Springwood application
在Springwood应用程序中注释
and at runtime at production one time
在生产时一次运行
nothing is different so it's just it
没有什么不同，仅此而已
basically just says okay I'm opting into
基本上只是说好，我选择加入
this package structure because we can
这种包装结构，因为我们可以
then later on in the tests do certain
然后在测试中确定
stuff to do that or we can do stuff by
要做的事情，或者我们可以通过
analyzing that structure
分析那个结构
you have them right so I just I show you
你说得对，所以我给你看
that in a psych so we have this kind of
在心理上，所以我们有这种
this package structure here you should
这个包结构你应该在这里
see you should see that I hope everyone
看到你应该看到我希望大家
in the back can sort of see that you see
在后面可以看到你看到的
a lot of like a lot of business packages
很像很多商务套餐
there's just more than what I had on the
不仅仅是我拥有的
slides there's like the accountancy
幻灯片像会计
there's payment support user accounts
有付款支持用户帐户
what-have-you
你有什么
it's just it's the fundamental idea is
只是它的基本思想是
that you have these packages right we
你有这些包对我们
also have sub-packages the the web one
网上也有分包
down there we can use that but what we
在那里，我们可以使用它，但是我们
can now do on there now is API where you
现在可以在那里执行API
can basically go ahead and say I think I
基本上可以说我想我
should have that somewhere even where
应该在某个地方
you start with something like that in a
你从这样的东西开始
test and that first line here modules of
测试，这里的第一行模块
sales point sample that's the that's the
销售点样本就是
fundamental application class and that
基本应用程序类
goes ahead and basically analyzes the
继续并基本分析
types within the packages and the spring
包装内的类型和弹簧
components for dependencies between the
组件之间的依赖关系
spring components and that implicitly
弹簧组件和隐式
creates a tree or at least the graph of
创建一棵树或至少图
dependencies between the modules which
模块之间的依赖关系
we can then work with and use to
然后，我们可以与并使用
actually help you analyze that and do
真正帮助您分析并做到
certain things to it and that's what I
某些事情，这就是我
want I want to get into going forward
想要我想前进
here right because when we now that we
在这里正确，因为当我们现在
know about the dependency graph between
了解之间的依赖关系图
your modules we can do the following we
您的模块，我们可以执行以下操作
can allow you to basically Express I
可以让你基本表达我
want to bootstrap that module and that
想引导那个模块
module only right that's pretty pretty
模块只对，这很漂亮
easy and it's it's something that's
很简单，这就是
built on the spring boot support testing
建立在Spring Boot支持测试上
support that has already been there for
已经存在的支持
quite a while we have always had these
我们已经有一段时间了
kind of the support for layer
对层的支持
annotations right so that's that's
正确的注释，就是这样
basically our spring boot testing
基本上我们的 spring boot 测试
annotations data JPA test data Mongo
批注数据JPA测试数据Mongo
test I think is
我认为是测试
in there that just would like from your
在那只是想从你那里
spring application in a boot in a test
在启动中测试中的spring应用程序
only bootstrap the repositories it would
只引导它会存储的存储库
not bootstrap any services or or
不引导任何服务或
components what have you no spring MVC
组件你没有弹簧的MVC
mostly for the reason to optimize for
主要是为了进行优化的原因
for speed right so - for for bootstrap
为了提高速度，所以-对于引导
time the same for web MVC test they
Web MVC测试的时间相同
would put stop Jackson and it would
将阻止杰克逊，它将
bootstrap spring and we see but all the
引导春天，我们看到但所有
controllers would have to be mocked out
控制器将不得不被模拟
so the question is when we do this for
所以问题是当我们这样做时
layers what would prevent us from doing
阻止我们做的事情
that for vertical slices for business
用于业务的垂直切片
sizes right so on that level and that's
大小合适，在那个水平上，那是
basically what on top of that on the the
基本上在
module test annotation basically is so
模块测试注释基本上是这样
you'd go ahead and in your integration
您将继续进行整合
test let's go ahead we have this
测试让我们继续吧，我们有这个
integration test here it's in the module
集成测试在模块中
package so in in one of the business
包在业务之一
packages and it says add module tests
软件包，并说添加模块测试
and that basically goes ahead an on test
基本上就可以进行测试了
bootstrap starts that that analysis of
引导程序开始对
the module structure and then finds out
模块的结构，然后找出
okay all the components that are just in
好吧，所有的组件都在里面
that package and reconfigures the boot
该软件包并重新配置启动
spring bootstrap to only see that
spring boot 只能看到
package effectively right components
有效包装正确的组件
getting JPA entity scanning all that
让JPA实体扫描所有内容
kind of stuff alright so let's see that
好东西，让我们来看看
in action for the catalog because why
在目录中起作用，因为为什么
why do we start with the catalog it's
为什么我们从目录开始
the easiest thing because it doesn't
最简单的事情，因为它没有
have any any outgoing dependencies so
有任何传出的依赖，所以
let's let's see how that works that's
让我们看看它是如何工作的
not here we go sorry about that catalog
不在这里，我们对该目录感到抱歉
integration test so it for now it's just
集成测试，所以现在
a spring boot test I can run it and then
spring boot 测试，我可以运行它，然后
I hope that's visible for everyone in
我希望每个人都可以看到
the back there's nothing special
后面没有什么特别的
happening it's just a ten tests that
只是十个测试
have been executed the entire
已全部执行
application was bootstraps like all the
应用程序是像所有
unrelated stuff everything that doesn't
无关的东西
have anything to do with catalogs has
与目录有关
also be both strapped and of course
也被捆绑，当然
checked which is a bit of a downside
检查这是一个缺点
even because
即使因为
if you now break some kind of
如果你现在打破某种
dependencies like spring beam
像Spring Beam这样的依赖
dependencies or something in an
依赖或某物
unrelated package these tests will fail
不相关的程序包，这些测试将失败
because of because of that right so it's
因为因为那个权利所以
not it's not really isolated so what we
不是它不是真的孤立，所以我们
can do instead is we can switch to the
可以代替的是我们可以切换到
add module test annotation nevermind the
添加模块测试注释不要介意
verifier automatically falls here I'm
验证程序自动落在这里
going to get back to that in a second
再过一秒钟
but I'm going to rerun the tests and
但我要重新运行测试，
then you will see slightly different
那么您会看到略有不同
output you will be told that okay we're
输出，您将被告知，好的，我们
starting a module test for sales point
开始对销售点进行模块测试
catalog geez that screen resolution is a
目录geez屏幕分辨率是
bit hard to work with
有点辛苦
that's the module that's that's
那是那个模块
bootstrap so it has a logical name it
引导程序，所以它有一个逻辑名称
has a base package we inspect all the
有一个基本包装，我们检查所有
spring beans that are in the in that
那个里面的春豆
very package and find out about
非常包装，并找出有关
references to other spring beans and we
参考其他春豆，我们
haven't found any that's why we say here
还没找到，所以我们在这里说
and we have a single spring bean in here
我们这里有一个春豆
it's a public one that's why we have a
这是一个公共的，这就是为什么我们有一个
plus year public class I could get back
再加上一年的公共课，我可以回来
to that in a second and we have a lot of
一秒钟，我们有很多
a couple of shared modules that's
几个共享模块
something I have set up I don't want to
我已经设置的东西我不想
go into it's basically a mechanism to
基本上是一种机制
from all the modules that we have
从我们拥有的所有模块中
available to always bootstrap these as
可随时将其引导为
well and not having to explicitly
好，而不必显式
declare those it's something you can
声明那些是可以的
tweak in the add module is a notation
在添加模块中进行调整是一种表示法
but let's spare that for now for the
但让我们暂时将其保留下来
sake of simplicity
为了简单
so it basically then tells you which
所以它基本上会告诉您
modules are bootstrapped and you see the
模块被引导，您会看到
user account modules bootstrap the core
用户帐户模块引导核心
modules but bootstrap and support one
模块，但引导并支持一个
and then it tells you it reconfigures
然后告诉您重新配置
the auto configuration and entity
自动配置和实体
scanning to those packages and that's
扫描到那些包，那就是
and that just like works as before with
就像以前一样
the upside that any kind of like arrows
任何类似箭头的好处
or bootstrap errors that would have been
或引导错误
called by other modules not actually
并非由其他模块实际调用
breaking this test right that's that's
打破这个测试的权利就是
pretty much it
差不多
all right so far so easy um let's go
到目前为止一切顺利，让我们开始吧
ahead and have a look at at the
向前看一下
inventory what you see here and what's
盘点您在这里看到的是什么
probably some of you might have realized
也许你们当中有些人已经意识到
already is that we have a cyclic
已经是我们有一个循环
relationship between the orders package
订单包之间的关系
and the inventory and that's actually an
和库存，实际上是
architectural violation and we're going
建筑违规，我们要去
to get that reported if we want to if we
得到我们想要的报告
try to if we try to bootstrap the
尝试如果我们尝试引导
inventory test
库存测试
there we go
我们去
[Music]
[音乐]
that's weird which I should fail I hope
那很奇怪，我应该失败，我希望
it fails
它失败
no it doesn't nice I probably checked
不，不好，我可能检查过
out the wrong one sec yes I got lost in
错了一秒钟，是的，我迷路了
the history I need to check out there
我需要检查的历史
where's my cursor there are this I need
我的光标在哪里，我需要这个
to check out the right
签出正确的
oh well that works well the right gosh
哦，很好，对了，不错
what is it sales point imperative state
什么是销售点命令状态
we need to check out that one so I'm
我们需要检查一个，所以我
sorry for that
对此感到抱歉
how are you there
你好吗
looks like I'll come in check out that
好像我进去看看
should be it well okay that looks
看起来应该还可以吗
different now
现在不同
um just a quick refresh hoping that
嗯，只是快速刷新，希望
everything I am hoping that everything
我希望一切
breaks as expected it doesn't
打破预期，没有
oh well yeah it it's it's not supposed
哦，是的，这不是应该的
to you see we have this verify
给你看，我们有这个验证
automatically set to false that's
自动设置为false
because I had this architectural
因为我有这个建筑
violation built in all the time and to
违规行为始终存在
actually get this running in the first
实际在第一时间运行
place or not sailing in the first place
放在第一位还是不在第一位
I had to disable the verification so if
我必须禁用验证，所以如果
I now go ahead and switch that for that
我现在继续将其切换为
which is basically enabling the
这基本上使
verification then fingers crossed this
验证然后手指越过这个
should not fail yeah all right so it
不应该失败，好吧，所以
basically reports that we have an
基本上说我们有一个
architectural cycle between inventory in
库存之间的架构周期
order where is this coming from this
命令这是从哪里来的
comes from the fact that we need to go
来自我们需要走的事实
back here that our order implementation
回到这里，我们的订单执行
has a I basically had to break it Jesus
我基本上不得不打破它耶稣
I had to break it to introduce this
我不得不打破它来介绍这个
violation because of course if you like
违反当然是因为如果你喜欢
I prepared this off site it should have
我准备了这个应该有的场外
been it doesn't it shouldn't actually
不是吗，实际上不应该
have that violation in the first place
首先有违规行为
but to just show you what I wanted to
但只是向您展示我想要的
shoot at and I had to introduce it so
射击，所以我必须介绍一下
what this kind of thing does is on
这种事情在做什么
completion of the order we actively
我们积极完成订单
invoke the inventory to update the
调用清单以更新
inventory and you see that method
库存，您会看到该方法
signature here takes an order and that
签名在这里接受命令
inventory lives in the other in the
库存生活在另一个
other package which means there's no a
其他包装，这意味着没有
cyclic relationship between inventory in
存货之间的周期性关系
order right order needs to know about
订购正确的订单需要了解
the inventory component it needs to have
它需要拥有的库存组件
that while when I want to bootstrap the
当我想引导
order that that order module it needs to
订购需要的订单模块
access that inventory beam but at the
访问该库存光束，但在
same time we have a type dependency on
同时我们对
order within that method here
在此方法中订购
so right it's just that that that exact
是的，就是那个确切的
thing here so what we can do and that's
事情在这里，所以我们能做的就是
why I basically that's why I already
为什么我基本上这就是为什么我已经
checked out that other Jesus that arrow
签出另一个耶稣那个箭头
is sort of gum yeah I'll check out
是一种口香糖，我会退房
commit again check out and did that work
再次提交签出并完成该工作
get hard to check out spring now there
现在很难去检查春天
we go all right yeah go away
我们走了，是的，走了
so um refreshing this my gosh why is it
嗯，这让我耳目一新，为什么
a real gun so I fixed that
真正的枪，所以我固定了
implementation or that that issue by
实施或那个问题
using something that much it was just
使用的东西仅仅是
showing in the talk before so we have
之前在谈话中显示，所以我们有
support to publish application events in
支持在以下位置发布应用程序事件
spring spring data we have at dis
弹簧弹簧数据我们在dis
support for quite a while already which
支持已经有一段时间了
means that we can change the
意味着我们可以改变
implementation to actually just look
实现实际上只是看
something like this so instead of
这样的事情，所以而不是
actively invoking the component in the
积极调用
other in the other module we just raisin
其他在其他模块中，我们只是葡萄干
events and we do that by using the
事件，我们通过使用
spring data abstract aggregate root
spring data 摘要聚合根
capabilities to register an event of
注册事件的能力
order completed which then publishes an
订单完成，然后发布
event to the spring application event
事件到春季申请事件
bus which then in this case here invokes
然后在这种情况下在这里调用的总线
an event listener on the ITA inventory
ITA清单上的事件侦听器
order this thing here basically that
在这里订购这东西基本上
event listener is its trigger it why is
事件监听器是它的触发器，为什么
that important and let me get back to
如此重要，让我回到
the slide deck so we basically replaced
滑盖，所以我们基本上更换了
that component dependency to inventory
该组件对库存的依赖性
with publishing and events and the
与发布和事件以及
inventory just listening for that event
只是听那个事件的清单
that's important because we now we sort
这很重要，因为我们现在我们进行排序
of broke the the dependency cycle and we
打破了依赖周期，我们
don't need the inventory to act
不需要采取行动
bootstrapped when we run the orders
当我们运行订单时启动
system right so it's or the orders
系统的权利，所以它或命令
module let's go back to the inventory
模块，让我们回到库存
tests and this now should work without
测试，现在应该可以在没有
and it actually work you've seen it
它确实有效，您已经看到了
before
之前
it should now work and not report the
现在应该可以正常工作了，而不是报告
violation anymore the the bottom line
违反了底线
this there's a two-fold bottom line here
这有两个底线
the one is that you should critically
一个是你应该批判
review all the the cross module
复习所有交叉模块
component injections because the more
组分注射，因为更多
you have of that
你有那个
the more stuff you actually have to
您实际需要的更多东西
bootstrap if you want to like bootstrap
如果你想喜欢bootstrap
that single module like if you have a
该单个模块，例如，如果您有一个
let's say orders have this dependency to
假设订单对此具有依赖性
inventory so we want to run we want to
库存，所以我们要运行，我们要
bootstrap orders we have to bootstrap
自举命令，我们必须自举
inventory as well so the less of these
库存也一样
connections you have the easier it is to
连接变得更容易
start that to test that thing in
开始测试那个东西
isolation and the other thing is that
隔离，另一件事是
this can usually be achieved by just
这通常可以通过
publishing an event it's it's not even
发布事件，甚至没有
like involving any kind of Kafka or or a
例如涉及任何种类的卡夫卡或
cross process event publication it's
跨流程事件发布
just using it the immense a mechanism
只是使用它一个巨大的机制
internally aunt right indeed the third
内部阿姨确实是第三个
thing actually that's what I wanted to
其实这就是我想要的
mention is let's see that you that you
提及是让我们看到你
should like to have understood that if
想知道如果
you actually introduced a cyclic
您实际上引入了循环
dependency by accident setting up your
偶然地建立您的依赖
tests like this would actually basically
基本上这样的测试
reveal that right so it's not that they
揭示那个权利，所以不是他们
go unnoticed which is usually the the
被忽视通常是
reason for for the degradation of the
退化的原因
structure in the in the system 20
系统20中的结构
minutes okay
分钟还可以
so the thing is that so module is
所以事情是这样的模块是
basically understands and differentiates
基本了解和区分
between three types of dependencies as
在三种类型的依赖之间
of today I haven't really found an
今天我还没有真正找到
important third cat or fourth category
重要的第三只猫或第四类
if you have happened to play with it and
如果您碰巧玩过它，
think there should be things should be
认为应该有东西应该
improved please provide feedback it's
改善了，请提供反馈
not always appreciated so simple type
并不总是很欣赏如此简单的类型
dependencies is
依赖是
what just like as I said inventory item
就像我说的库存物品一样
to to product for example right simple
以产品为例简单
type dependencies
类型依赖
there's component dependencies so we
存在组件依赖性，所以我们
analyze spring beans declared in the in
分析在中声明的春豆
the modules for constructor parameters
构造函数参数的模块
yes even for field injection although
是的，即使是现场注入，虽然
that's of course also rejected and you
那当然也被拒绝了，你
turn on the verification or which is
打开验证或
enabled by default and there is events
默认情况下启用，并且有事件
and event listeners because yeah event
和事件监听器，因为是事件
listeners usually work exactly the other
聆听者通常与其他人完全一样
way around right if you the inventory is
如果您的库存是正确的
listening for order events there is no
听订单事件没有
dependency no module dependency between
依赖之间没有模块依赖
inventory and and orders but it's rather
库存和订单，但它相当
the other way around was we publish the
另一种方法是我们发布
the event for the other one and to
另一个事件
listen to the ones that you want to
听你想听的
critically review other component
严格审查其他组件
dependencies because they actually make
依赖，因为它们实际上使
make your your testing life quite a bit
使您的测试生活相当长
complicated and I'm going to show you
复杂，我将向您展示
why by actually trying to move the
为什么通过实际尝试移动
orders tests to to the modulus testing
从测试到模量测试
infrastructure so we want we want to
基础设施，所以我们想要我们想要
test this thing actually in isolation
单独测试这个东西
and I'm going to show you how modulus is
我将向您展示模量如何
reports that there is some component
报告有一些成分
that is not bootstrapped but that's
那不是自举的，那是
required for the test to run so let's go
运行测试所需的，所以我们开始吧
to order tests right so this is the this
订购正确的测试，所以这是
is the order tests it again it's by as a
是命令再次对其进行测试
start it actually uses the spring booth
开始使用弹簧展台
tests so you see they are working we're
测试，以便您看到它们正在起作用，我们正在
using an abstract base class here it
在这里使用抽象基类
says when booth tests yada-yada-yada so
说摊位测试yada-yada-yada时
it's again as of now bootstrapping
现在又是自举
the the complete application so what we
完整的应用程序，所以我们
want to change this to is to use the
想要更改为使用
module tests annotation I
模块测试注解I
and I can go into into what the extra
我可以进入额外的内容
includes does for now all right we can
现在包括我们可以做到的
skip that I think I can get to that in a
跳过我认为我可以在
second so what I'm now expressing is I
第二，所以我现在要表达的是
want to bootstrap the orders module and
要引导订单模块，并
by accident I want to bootstrap the
我偶然地想引导
catalog as well but let's see what
目录，但让我们看看
happens if we do that and then I'm get
如果我们这样做就会发生，然后我得到
to get to you in a second
一秒钟到达你
so it's breaking we can sort of cancel
所以打破了，我们可以取消
that already because the G's yeah the
那是因为G是的
output should be should be telling
输出应该是应该告诉
enough on them on the first test case so
在第一个测试用例上就足够了
what you basically get is there's no
你基本上得到的是没有
qualifying being of business time
合格的营业时间
available if you remember in the in the
如果您记得在
slide deck I had there was a there was a
我曾经有一个幻灯片甲板
dependency on the business time module
依赖于业务时间模块
and that's presented through that
这是通过
private final filled business time that
私人最后的营业时间
is then it basically is exposed by the
然后它基本上就被暴露了
constructor created by a Lombok here so
龙目岛在这里创建的构造函数
we actually by that have set up a module
实际上，我们已经建立了一个模块
dependency between the order and the
订单与
time package this is where business time
时间包，这是营业时间
lives and there is a spring component
生活，有一个春天的组成部分
for that all right there's default
为此，默认情况下
business time it's an EDD service so
营业时间是EDD服务，所以
that means we of course cannot bootstrap
这意味着我们当然不能自举
orders tests in isolation because it
孤立地订购测试，因为它
needs that particular spring bean right
需要那个特别的四季豆
it needs that other module to run to
它需要其他模块来运行
satisfy the global dependency graph so
满足全局依赖图
there's two things that you can do now
您现在可以做两件事
the first thing is and that's actually
首先是，实际上
built into into spring boot
内置于弹簧靴
out-of-the-box is you can just define a
开箱即用的是，您可以定义一个
mock bean for that particular component
该特定组件的模拟bean
and you can run it run the test and then
然后您可以运行它运行测试，然后
you should see that like stuff just
你应该看到像东西
works right and that's actually I like
工作正常，这实际上是我喜欢的
that quite a lot because what you do is
那很多，因为你要做的是
you say I want to start the orders
你说我想开始下订单
module because it's a module test and to
模块，因为这是一个模块测试
actually make that work I have to mark
真正使我不得不做的工作
cook this component and that component
煮这个成分和那个成分
this component so you're pretty clearly
这个组件，所以你很清楚
describing like your module plus the
像模块一样描述
external dependencies right and
外部依赖权和
depending on what you want to do you
取决于你想做什么
could of course like then go ahead and
当然可以像然后继续
set up business time to actually like
设定营业时间以真正喜欢
mock interactions or what have you
模拟互动或你有什么
another approach to this isn't an
另一种方法不是
alternative is that you could go ahead
另一种是，你可以继续
and say well I might not just want to
说好吧，我可能不只是想要
bootstrap this particular module but all
引导此特定模块，但所有
direct dependencies of that module right
该模块的直接依赖权
so this would now include what's going
所以现在这包括正在发生的事情
on it's running now something I just ran
它正在运行，现在我刚运行了
it what's going on what
这是怎么回事
save that's cloud computing words so
保存那是云计算的话，所以
what do you see here let's have a look
你在这里看到什么让我们看一下
at the Lord output because that it's now
在耶和华的输出，因为现在
becoming interesting right so we find
变得有趣起来，所以我们发现
out that the orders module has has
订单模块有
module dependencies on user account and
用户帐户和
time
时间
so by this persistent order manager has
因此，通过此持久性订单经理，
probably has something like the user
可能有类似用户的东西
account manager injected there's an
客户经理注入了一个
orders repository you can see that there
订单存储库，您可以看到那里
are all like a package protected classes
都像一个受包保护的类
that's that little oh here and there was
那就是那里的那个小哦
a plus before if you remember and we
如果您还记得我们之前的加号，我们
also extra include the catalog in the
还额外包括目录
bootstrap phase and then that actually
引导阶段，然后实际上
means that these boot that these modules
意味着这些引导这些模块
are actually bootstrap
实际上是自举
right so you can get a pretty good
对的所以你可以得到一个很好的
overview what actually gets run and that
概述实际运行的内容
sort of helps you to just like okay now
可以帮助您立即好起来
the business module the actual business
业务模块实际业务
time component in this case would have
在这种情况下，时间部分将具有
been would have been run so what if what
已经可以运行了，如果怎么办
if seen by default is the standalone one
如果默认情况下显示为独立
it's basically just like run this module
基本上就像运行此模块一样
only and whatever kind of references out
只是，无论哪种参考
of the module you have you need to mock
您需要模拟的模块
them that's the one way of doing it you
他们是做到这一点的一种方法
can use a the direct dependencies
可以使用直接依赖
bootstrap mode that would just like
引导模式，就像
include one one layer more or one one
包括一层以上或一层
transitive dependency more and there's
传递依存关系越来越多
also that all dependencies mode which
还有所有依赖模式
basically from the entire module graph
基本上从整个模块图
just picks the node and just runs
只是选择节点并运行
everything that's needed downstream but
下游需要的一切，但
not everything unrelated all right so
不是所有无关的东西都可以
that that would just just work as well
那也将很好地工作
it's pretty much the it's the the
这几乎是
closest you can get to spring boot tests
最接近弹簧启动测试的地方
but avoiding to bootstrap all the all
但避免全部自举
the other modules that you don't need in
您不需要的其他模块
this case
这个案例
all right so that's the test support
好的，这就是测试支持
that's pretty helpful I think already
我认为已经很有帮助
probably needs a bit of getting used to
可能需要一点习惯
to like manage these these module
喜欢管理这些模块
dependencies it's something that
依赖关系
first when you when you when you haven't
首先当你当你没有
like been used to that kind of stuff it
就像习惯了那种东西
feels like okay I'm constantly getting
感觉还可以，我不断
the structure of my system in the face
我脸上的系统结构
basically or basically held held before
基本上或以前举行过
me but it's pretty pretty neat to
我，但很整洁
actually avoid introducing any kind of
实际上避免引入任何形式的
unwanted unwanted dependencies right
有害的有害依赖权
what we also do in the verification step
我们在验证步骤中也做了什么
is that based on the module packages we
是基于模块包
ensure that they are cycle free so
确保它们无循环，因此
that's actually why that why those why
这就是为什么为什么那那些为什么
those those bootstraps without that
那些没有那个的引导
verify automatically equals false flag
自动验证等于假标志
failed in the first place right and that
首先失败了，那
actually gives you a lot of like
实际上给你很多像
confidence that you have a sort of well
相信自己有一种健康
structured module set up because if it's
结构化模块设置是因为
if there's no cycles in there there's
如果那里没有循环
like a directed acyclic graph and you
像有向无环图，而你
sort of know that you will have leaf
有点知道你会有叶子
modules and you will have root modules
模块，您将拥有根模块
that will just depend on others so the
那将取决于其他人，所以
chances are that if you have a
如果您有一个机会
cycle-free module arrangement then that
那么无周期的模块布置
your system is pretty decently
您的系统相当不错
structured in the first place without
首先没有任何结构
you defining explicit dependencies and
您定义显式依赖项，并且
what have you all right
你还好吗
there's more to this we can we can sort
还有更多我们可以分类的东西
of hide components from other modules
其他模块的隐藏组件
you can define let's say this is the API
您可以定义，假设这是API
package this is an implementation
包这是一个实现
package I wanted I wanted to skip that
我想跳过的包裹
that for now just because of to save a
现在只是因为保存一个
bit of time and want to get to something
有点时间，想去点什么
and I find kind of interesting which is
我觉得很有趣
the documentation aspect because usually
文档方面，因为通常
you start with that set of boxes on and
你从那组盒子开始
on and on a PowerPoint deck and then you
在PowerPoint卡座上和之后
just put that into code by some means
只是通过某种方式将其放入代码中
and when as soon as stuff sort of
以及什么时候
evolves
进化
it's pretty hard to keep up I keep the
跟上我很难跟上
the documentation up-to-date and like if
文档是最新的，如果
let's say you introduce another
假设您介绍了另一个
dependency between from one module to
从一个模块到
another and the thing is just as with
另一个，事情就像
all we got all this kind of structural
所有我们得到的都是这种结构
analysis without really doing much to
分析并没有做太多事情
the application except changing that one
该应用程序，除了更改那个
annotation we can use that that
注释，我们可以使用
structural information that you that you
你的结构信息
provided implicitly provided to render
提供隐式提供
out like diagrams that reflect the
像反映了
actual state of the system right and
系统权限的实际状态和
that kind of is there's just a tiny API
那里只有一个很小的API
that you can use for to create those
您可以用来创建这些
diagrams again in a test usually and
通常在测试中再次绘制图表，
that is looks something like this I can
看起来像这样我可以
pull that up a bit so you again say ok
把它拉起来，所以你再说一遍
go ahead please analyze the the module
继续，请分析模块
structure then you use that document
结构，然后您使用该文档
module and there's a bit of a couple of
模块，还有一些
options that you can define what should
您可以定义的选项
go into the diagram what shouldn't and
进入图表中不应该的，
then there's just a tiny just that very
然后只有一个很小的
method here basically saying okay just
这里的方法基本上说好吧
dump me all the the modules as plant UML
将所有模块转储为工厂UML
diagrams or just take every module and
图或只是采取每个模块和
create an a diagram for every module way
为每种模块方式创建图表
you say a diagram for every module these
您为每个模块说一个图表
ones down here actually include the
这里的那些实际上包括
module like under suspicion basically
基本上像怀疑的模块
and just that the diagram that contains
只是其中包含的图
all the incoming dependencies to that
所有传入的依赖项
particular module and all the outgoing
特定的模块和所有传出的
dependencies so it's basically put this
依赖关系，基本上就是这样
in the focus and like what's the contact
在焦点上，像是什么联系
what context does that module live in
该模块位于什么环境中
where is the former here is just
前者在哪里
basically the kitchen sink everything
基本上厨房洗碗
and in its arrangements as you see in
并按照您在
the project we just like write them out
我们就像把它们写出来的项目
you can of course define where the stuff
您当然可以定义这些东西在哪里
is going to be written what files what
将要写什么文件什么
the what the file name patterns are but
文件名模式是什么，但是
ultimately this stuff ends up in implant
最终这些东西最终植入
UML modules which I usually recommend to
我通常建议的UML模块
include into asciidoctor
纳入asciidoctor
documentation and then we're just like
文档，然后我们就像
something like this then right so it's
这样的东西然后正确的是
kind of like it's that's the that's the
有点像是
module the module diagram for the order
订单模块图
component and it differentiates again
成分，并再次与众不同
like the cup the different dependency
像杯子一样依赖
types saying the users the users
类型说用户，用户
dependency type is basically a spring
依赖类型基本上是弹簧
component being reference everything
组件被引用一切
else depends on is just a type
其他取决于只是一种
dependency there's also the event in the
依赖也有事件在
over and the overall diagram it also
结束，整体图也
shows the the listens to dependency
显示监听依赖
relationship that's up here as you see
就像你看到的那样
and that's basically what we what we
这基本上就是我们所要
sort of like refactor to when we
有点像重构当我们
basically undid the the breakage that
基本上消除了破损
are introduced for for the sake of of
被引入是为了
showing that stuff so let's see
显示这些东西，让我们看看
vandalism so just getting that kind of
故意破坏，所以
stuff from let's say a from like your
假设您喜欢的东西
existing code arrangement for free
现有代码安排免费
basically is kind of its kind of neat I
基本上是一种整洁的我
think all right so what kind of context
认为没事，那么什么样的背景
does module lists now live in because
现在是否存在模块列表，因为
they're it's it's not the first time
他们是这不是第一次
that someone tried to put some structure
有人试图放一些结构
in place right in in these new systems
在这些新系统中就位
one alternative that you could start
您可以开始的另一种选择
with is multiple artifacts which means I
与是多个文物，这意味着我
could go ahead and could have created a
可以继续，并可能已经创造了一个
maven module for all these individual
适用于所有这些个人的Maven模块
business modules right and then have
正确的业务模块，然后拥有
defined the dependencies in my amazing
定义了我惊人的依赖
dependency descriptor and then just have
依赖描述符，然后有
that or use that to basically control
或使用它来基本控制
the dependencies because may even
依赖，因为甚至
already prevent cyclic dependencies
已经防止循环依赖
between modules so that's kind of neat
在模块之间，这样很整洁
right so that would have been an
对的，那本来是
alternative approach that's pretty fine
很好的替代方法
you can do that you can still do that
你可以做到，你仍然可以做到
even with modulus we don't care in which
即使有模数，我们也不在乎
artifact these these things live all
这些东西都是人造的
that matters is what your class path
重要的是你上课的路径
look like
看起来像
right the package is the package
对的包裹就是包裹
structure on your class plan and we're
在您的课程计划中进行结构调整，我们
sort of inspecting that what's also nice
有点检查，这也很好
is that I can I can actually test a
是我可以实际测试一个
module in isolation because I have
孤立模块，因为我有
everything there the thing is that as
那里的一切就是
soon as I need to pull in other modules
我需要引入其他模块时
that help me testing as I pulled in the
当我拉入
catalog module in the orders test
订单测试中的目录模块
because I wanted to set up some products
因为我想设置一些产品
to actually put into the order and
实际输入订单并
that's getting a bit complicated because
这变得有点复杂，因为
the dependency arrangement in a module
模块中的依存关系安排
usually is a static one right so you
通常是静态权利，所以您
declare that once and then all of your
一遍又一遍地宣布
tests sort of have to live with that
测试有点必须忍受
arranger and that's actually the or
编曲，实际上是
there's two more downsides with that
还有两个缺点
with a module per business package I
每个业务包都有一个模块I
would have ended up with what is it
最终会是什么
twelve main modules and twelve pom files
十二个主要模块和十二个pom文件
that sort of all relate to each other
那种彼此相关
I've been in a project where even a
我去过一个项目，甚至
simple module setup would end up with 36
简单的模块设置将以36结尾
something maven modules so that can be a
一些Maven模块，因此可以是
bit overwhelming so why not just keep
有点不知所措，所以为什么不保持
them all together because we're going to
他们在一起，因为我们要
deploy them all at once anyway and just
无论如何立即部署它们
like try to try to maintain the
喜欢尝试维护
structure in a different way and what it
结构以不同的方式及其作用
also means is that unlike the internal
也意味着不同于内部
structure is now all of a sudden visible
结构突然变得可见
to anyone on the outside so because of
给外面的人，因为
the jars probably getting published into
罐子可能被发布到
some maven repo right so someone else
一些行家回购权，所以别人
trying to use your your piece of
试图用你的
software which and then just have to
然后必须要做的软件
basically get together and select a
基本上聚在一起并选择一个
couple of of charges together another
几个指控一起
thing that you could try is the Java
您可以尝试的是Java
module system which I think there's even
我认为甚至有模块系统
a talk on it I have to see that later
关于它的谈话我以后要看
today that works pretty well as well it
今天效果还不错
has a couple of downsides that I find
我发现有一些缺点
rather limiting for especially for for
尤其是对于
this this kind of stuff
这种东西
Java modules fundamentally assumes that
Java模块从根本上假设
you have an artifact per module right so
每个模块都有一个工件，所以
there's no way you can have multiple
你不可能有多个
modules in an artifact at least right
工件中的模块至少正确
now I brought this up on on the
现在我把这个放在
on the mailing list already they're
在邮件列表中，他们已经
looking into it it might just not be
看着它可能不是
what they need because remember the Java
他们需要什么，因为记住Java
module system was invented to actually
模块系统实际上是发明的
be able to structure the JDK right it's
能够正确构建JDK
not a it at least I mean right now
至少现在不是我的意思
everyone thinks two things about it as
每个人都认为这有两件事
the Java module system supposed to be
Java模块系统应该是
used for your applications it's that
用于您的应用程序就是
that's not what it was built for at
那不是它原本的目的
least not originally and I can see a
至少不是最初的，我可以看到
couple of a couple of other things like
其他一些类似的事情
these are basically sort of getting in
这些基本上是进入
the way if you really want to want to
如果您真的想
take it to into a real world application
将其带入现实世界的应用程序
semantics of the opens key word is
打开关键字的语义是
that's a bit of reflection stuff because
那是一些反思的东西，因为
you basically have a package that or
你基本上有一个包装，或
packages that you basically declare API
基本声明API的软件包
but there's no no fine grained control
但没有细粒度的控制
of over-over what's exposed so people
过度暴露的东西，所以人们
start making separate packages and
开始制作单独的包装，
public types and whatnot so if you want
公共类型，如果需要的话
to details on that feel free to get to
可以随时获得有关该细节的信息
catch me later and there's no no support
以后抓我，没有支持
to dynamically assemble modules for
动态组装模块
tests right so that's that's kind of the
测试正确，所以这就是
stuff that I I described before there's
我之前描述过的东西
external tools that you can use things
可以使用事物的外部工具
like JQ assistant sonogram J depends and
就像JQ辅助超声检查图J取决于
I'd recommend you to do that because
我建议您这样做，因为
especially I'm a bit familiar with JQ
特别是我对JQ有点熟悉
assistant it's a it's a tool that
助手，这是一个工具
basically pulls all yours all your your
基本上把你所有的拉
code base into a new forge a graph
代码库到新的伪造图中
database and allows you to query the
数据库，并允许您查询
database and through the queries
数据库并通过查询
actually define rules it's incredibly
实际上定义了难以置信的规则
powerful it's it's not of course it
功能强大，当然不是
would strain to to the source code but
会压缩到源代码，但是
can also inspect your get commits and
也可以检查您的提交并
correlate these things so there's a lot
关联这些东西，所以有很多
of power in these tools however they are
这些工具的力量
usually more expensive to run and they
通常运行起来比较昂贵，他们
usually run during the build right and
通常在构建权期间运行
if I run stuff during the build it's
如果我在构建过程中运行东西
hard or if I delays that those checks to
辛苦或者如果我延迟这些检查
the build there's no way I can use that
构建没有办法我可以使用它
structural information that I could
我可以的结构信息
maybe gain from within the test cases
也许从测试用例中受益
right so it's kind of I want earlier
对，所以我想早一点
feedback ideally I would have like see
理想情况下，我希望看到反馈
those those structural by
那些由
relations even through the compiler and
关系，甚至通过编译器
that's a cool tool called detective I
那是一个很酷的工具，叫做侦探一
think by guna morning they build an apt
认为在古纳早上他们会建造一个
processor that based on a JSON file sort
基于JSON文件排序的处理器
of those similar things that we do and
我们所做的类似事情
it's it's not like imposing those
这不是像强加那些
packaged constraints so you have to do a
打包的约束，因此您必须
bit more but at the same time it
多一点，但同时
basically causes the compiler or to get
基本上导致编译器或获取
you the the red underlines in your app
您的应用中的红色下划线
in your in your editor already so that's
在您的编辑器中已经
something to look into it's it's
要研究的东西是
definitely as I said Jake your assistant
就像我说的那样，杰克是你的助手
you can do way more things with it then
你可以用它做更多的事情
what I basically try to do with modulus
我基本上尝试使用模数
with distance to development workflow I
与开发流程的距离我
mean when do you actually get the
意思是你什么时候真正得到
feedback and what does this mean in
反馈，这意味着什么
terms of like the the ability to to
像
implement certain things right so the
正确执行某些事情，这样
first thing is the compiler second the
首先是编译器第二
second distant thing is the test and the
第二个遥远的东西是测试和
third distant thing is this is the build
第三个遥远的东西是这是构建
system right so three iterates
系统正确，所以三个迭代
convention to map context to packages
将上下文映射到包的约定
that allows us to reason about the
这使我们能够对
module the modular structure of your
模块您的模块化结构
system we can then build support on that
系统，我们可以在此基础上建立支持
on top of that to actually bootstrap
最重要的是实际引导
parts of your system there's even more
系统的更多部分
to that in terms of like more complex
就好像更复杂
package arrangements right arrange
包装安排权安排
packages with with that have internal
与的软件包具有内部
packages and access rules about that and
有关的软件包和访问规则，以及
you can actually go ahead and derive
你实际上可以继续推导
documentation from it from that
从中得到的文档
structure that you sort of implicitly
您隐式排序的结构
created there's the project website on
创建了项目网站
github and there are two talks I'd
github，我有两个演讲
recommend that sort of discuss similar
建议类似的讨论
ideas modular monolith is Simon Brown
想法模块化整体是西蒙·布朗
probably I mean I don't have to talk
大概我的意思是我不必讲话
about too much about him discussing that
关于他的讨论太多了
package by component idea mostly in
按组件包装的想法主要在
there talk Majestic modular model is I
那里说雄伟的模块化模型是我
have to add that is from
必须添加来自
[Music]
[音乐]
you see me no no no the guy behind these
你看到我不，不，不，这些背后的家伙
this this database stuff to flyweight
这个数据库的东西飞起来
who's the right flyweight I'm sorry
谁是最合适的轻量级对不起
about that
关于那个
um click on the link thank you
嗯，点击链接谢谢
you'll find out refactoring sis to
您会发现重构SIS
system of systems there's a couple of
系统的系统有几个
recordings that's the talk of mine and
录音就是我的话题
basically touching touching the idea
基本上是动人的想法
that I've just shown you implemented in
我刚刚展示过您在
a couple of places that's it
就是几个地方
I'll be around until tomorrow afternoon
我会一直待到明天下午
thanks for your attention if you have
感谢您的关注，如果您有
any questions happen too happy to answer
发生任何问题都乐于回答
them
他们
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]